[upbeat music]
[欢快音乐]
- I'm starving.
我饿死了。
- Me too. - There's food in the fridge.
我也是。冰箱里有吃的。
- [groans]
[呻吟]
All the way over there?
那么远？
You go.
你去。
- No, you go.
不，你去。
- You go! - No, you go!
你去！不，你去！
- No, you go!
不，你去！
- Go!
去！
- Nobody has to go! We can just reach the fridge from here using the grabber.
- 没人非得去！我们可以用抓取器从这里直接够到冰箱。
- Good idea. Where's the grabber?
- 好主意。抓取器在哪儿？
[laughter]
[笑声]
[all straining]
[大家都在用力]
- All the way over there?
- 那么远？
You get it.
你去拿。
- No, you get it. - No, you get it.
- 不，你去拿。 - 不，你去拿。
- Fine!
- 好吧！
I'll get it.
我去拿。
[laughter]
[笑声]
[grabber clicks]
[抓取器点击声]
[scrunches]
[沙沙声]
Nope, won't reach.
不，够不着。
- Hello, boys.
- 嗨，男孩们。
You're looking at the two girls who're about to have...
你们正在看着两个即将拥有...
the best summer ever.
最棒的夏天。
- Us, too.
- 我们也是。
As soon as we get a longer grabber.
一旦我们拿到更长的抓取器。
- While you guys are sitting around, wasting your summer,
- 当你们坐在这里，浪费你们的夏天，
Mae and I will be making money from our fun, new jobs.
梅和我将通过我们有趣的新工作赚钱。
- At the only man-made beach in Colorado!
- 在科罗拉多州唯一的人造海滩！
- We're working at the Boulderly Hills
- 我们将在博尔德山工作
Country Club kids-only beach club.
- 乡村俱乐部儿童专属海滩俱乐部。
- No way! - The B.H.C.C. K.O.B.C?
- 不可能！ - 博尔德山乡村俱乐部儿童专属海滩俱乐部？
- You bet your B.U.T.T.
- 你绝对可以相信。
And when we aren't working, we get to use the wave pool,
而且当我们不工作时，我们可以使用波浪池，
beach volleyball courts, get manis--
海滩排球场，做美甲——
- Pedis-- both: Mani-pedis!
- 美足—— 两人齐声：美甲美足！
- Wow.
- 哇。
You guys are real go-getters.
你们这些人真是积极主动。
- Yeah. I've got a fun job for you go-getters.
是啊。我有个好玩的任务给你们这些积极的人。
How about you go get us some food?
怎么样，去给我们弄点吃的吧？
- Happy to.
乐意之至。
- [groans]
（呻吟声）
- You get it.
你去拿。
- You get it. - No, you get it!
- We need the grabber.
不，你去拿！
- The go-getter grabbed the grabber!
我们需要取物夹。
- Go get her!
积极分子拿到了取物夹！
- Grab her! - [sighs]
抓住她！ - [叹气]
- We need a go-getter grabber grabber.
我们需要一个积极进取的抓取器。
- I got this.
我来搞定。
I grabbed it!
我抓住了！
[laughter]
[笑声]
- Okay.
好吧。
[clicks] - [groans]
[点击声] - [呻吟]
This thing is useless.
这东西没用。
♪ ♪
[overlapping chatter]
[重叠的交谈声]
- I can't believe we're here.
- 真不敢相信我们在这里。
- I know, this is so exciting.
- 我知道，这太令人兴奋了。
- All right, let's get to work.
- 好吧，我们开始工作吧。
Mae, you're the hostess.
梅，你是主持人。
When people come in, you greet 'em and seat 'em.
当人们进来时，你迎接他们并安排座位。
Dawn, you're waiting tables.
道恩，你负责餐桌服务。
So when people come in--
所以当人们进来时——
- I treat 'em and feed 'em?
- 我招待他们并给他们食物？
- I do the rhymes here. Okay, Dawn?
- 我在这里负责说唱。好吗，道恩？
Now if you're able, there's your first table.
现在如果你能行，那是你的第一桌。
And that's how it's done, hon.
就是这样，亲爱的。
- Looks like I'm the hostess with the most-ess.
- 看来我成了最棒的女主人。
- I do the rhymes!
- 我负责说唱！
- All right, Mae.
- 好的，梅。
Our best summer ever starts right now.
我们最棒的夏天现在开始了。
Welcome to the Boulderly Hills Country Club!
欢迎来到博尔德山乡村俱乐部！
How can I help--
我怎么帮您--
You!
你！
- Us. - No!
- 我们。 - 不！
boys: Yes!
男孩们：是的！
- Our best summer ever starts now!
我们的最佳夏日现在开始！
Whoo!
喔！
[upbeat rock music]
[欢快的摇滚音乐]
♪ ♪
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na-na ♪ - ♪ Hey! ♪
♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐呐 ♪ ♪ 嘿！ ♪
- ♪ One, two, one-two-three-four! ♪
♪ 一，二，一二三四！ ♪
♪ ♪
- No, no, no, no, no, no.
不，不，不，不，不，不。
This is supposed to be my best summer ever!
这应该是我最好的夏天！
- Well, we took a long, hard look at ourselves, and realized
嗯，我们认真审视了自己，意识到
that sitting around in PJs all day was just denying
整天穿着睡衣无所事事只是在否认
the ladies all this.
女士们这一切。
- Yeah, who doesn't want to see hunks in trunks?
- 是啊，谁不想看到帅哥穿泳裤呢？
- I do the rhyming!
- 我负责押韵！
- How did you guys even get in here?
- 你们是怎么进来的？
- [chuckles] Turns out,
- [轻笑] 结果是，
Trey's parents are members,
特雷的父母是会员，
so he brought us.
所以他带我们进来的。
- Look, I don't want you no-getters
- 听着，我不希望你们这些无所作为的人
getting in the way of this...
妨碍到这件事...
[whispers] go-getter.
去争取者
- Why are you whispering?
- 你为什么窃窃私语？
- Because my boss does the rhyming.
- 因为我的老板负责押韵。
- My ears have never been sharper, Harper.
- Harper，我的耳朵从未如此灵敏过。
- Dawn, you've got nothing to worry about.
- Dawn，你没什么好担心的。
I mean, we're just here to chill, get tan,
我们只是来这里放松，晒黑，
and eat lots of food.
吃很多食物。
- You know, all the stuff you can't do
- 你知道，所有那些因为工作而不能做的事情。
because you're working.
- 是啊，Dawn，你真会选。
- Yeah, nice choice, Dawn.
说起工作，你去给我们拿点水来怎么样？
- Speaking of working,
how about you grab us some waters.
- Fine, that's easy enough. - I want flat water.
- I want bubbles. - I want a straw...
I'll make my own bubbles.
- Hi! - Whoa, whoa, whoa! - Say cheese!
- Wait, what are you guys still doing here?
- We wanted to see our baby at her first real job. - Okay, you've seen me, now go!
If you get caught around here, I could get in trouble.
- Okay, shh, shh. - Okay, one more for grandma. - Yeah.
- Here we go. - Okay, smile.
- 开始了。 - 好的，微笑。
- Now, Uncle Larry. - Smile!
- 现在，Larry叔叔。 - 微笑！
- Okay, okay. You need to go! Go!
- 好的，好的。你们得走了！快走！
- We love you so much! - Before my first real boss sees you!
- 我们非常爱你！ - 在我真正的第一个老板看到你们之前！
- Dawn...
your table's complaining that their "go-getter"
你的桌子那边在抱怨，他们的“积极分子”
hasn't gotten them their water yet.
还没给他们送水。
- Got it. I'm getting it.
- 知道了。我这就去。
- Good! Because I don't have time
- 好！因为我没时间
to babysit you.
来照顾你。
The head of the entertainment committee
娱乐委员会的主席
is throwing a huge party here tonight,
今晚在这里举办一个大型派对，
and it has to go perfectly, or it's my head.
必须完美无缺，否则就是我的责任。
- Wow, none of that rhymed.
- 哇，这些话都不押韵。
- I know!
- 我知道！
She makes me so nervous, I can't even rhyme around her.
她让我太紧张了，我甚至在她面前连押韵都做不到。
Here she comes!
她来了！
- Okay, relax.
- 好的，放松。
Let me talk to her, I'm a people person.
让我来跟她谈，我擅长与人打交道。
- Hello, Tori.
- 你好，托丽。
both: Madison?
两人同时: 麦迪逊?
- Oh! You two are members now?
- 哦! 你们现在是会员了?
- Oh, no, we work here.
- 哦, 不, 我们在这里工作。
- I know, I just wanted to make you say it.
- 我知道, 我只是想让你说出来。
- [feigned laughter]
- [假装笑声]
And they did!
他们确实说了!
- You know, I could just stand here all day
- 你知道, 我可以一整天站在这里
and make you say things.
让你说各种事情。
But...
但是...
I'm too busy getting ready for
我正忙着准备
my best summer ever kick-off party.
我为迎接有史以来最棒的夏日派对做准备。
- If you two mess this up for me,
如果你们两个搞砸了我的派对，
I'm sticking you in the basement to do the laundry.
我就把你们关在地下室洗衣服。
Yes, I'm back!
是的，我回来了！
Madison!
麦迪逊！
- Go-getter!
行动派！
Where's our waters?
我们的水呢？
- And my straw?
还有我的吸管呢？
Thank you.
谢谢。
- Ooh! A luxury cabana!
哦！豪华凉亭！
[gasps] Let's sneak in and see
[倒抽一口气] 我们偷偷溜进去看看
what our lives would be like
如果我们没有四个孩子
if we didn't have four kids.
我们的生活会是什么样子。
- Ooh, Momma never lost her wild side.
- 哦，妈妈从未失去她的野性。
- [laughs]
- [笑]
- There's a mini-fridge, a TV, a daybed!
- 这里有迷你冰箱，电视，日床！
It's like a tent for people who hate tents.
这就像是为讨厌帐篷的人准备的帐篷。
- Oh! You must be the Mermans.
- 哦！你们一定是默尔曼一家。
Oh, I thought you called to cancel. I was just about to open the cabana up to somebody else.
哦，我以为你们打电话取消了。我正准备把这个小屋让给别人。
- Well, now, we're not the-- - Oh, no, no, na! No, na! No, no, no, no, no.
- 呃，现在，我们不是—— - 哦，不，不，不！不，不！不，不，不，不，不。
[chuckles] No need.
[轻笑] 不需要。
We are the Mermans. That is totally us.
我们是Mermans。那完全是我们。
- [nervous chuckles]
[紧张的轻笑]
- Excellent!
太好了！
I'll go get your sushi platter.
我去拿你们的寿司拼盘。
- Mrs. Merman...
Merman太太...
[growls]
[低吼]
- Well, thank you, Mr. Merman.
嗯，谢谢你，Merman先生。
[both chuckling]
[两人轻笑]
- Momma's a wild one, today.
妈妈今天很狂野。
- Yeah...
是的...
and Daddy's drinking plant water.
而爸爸在喝植物水。
- Here you go, one B.H.C.C. B.L.T., extra B, easy T.
给你，一份B.H.C.C. B.L.T.，多加B，少加T。
- This next jam goes out to the pretty blonde girl.
下一首歌献给那位漂亮的金发女孩。
- Doh!
哎呀！
- She knows who she is.
她知道她是谁。
- Did you hear that?
你听到了吗？
I think I'm the pretty blonde girl.
我觉得我就是那位漂亮的金发女孩。
- You're definitely not the graceful blonde girl.
你绝对不是那位优雅的金发女孩。
- So, Trey, how does the food ordering work here?
那么，Trey，这里的点餐是怎么操作的？
- You just tell them what you want and when they bring it,
- 你只需告诉他们你想要什么，等他们送来时，
you sign for it.
你签收就行了。
Ooh! There's Mindy Gelzer.
哦！那是明迪·格尔泽。
It'd be a shame if she got sunburned.
她要是晒伤了就太可惜了。
Looks like she needs some SPF flirty.
看起来她需要一些SPF防晒霜。
[laughter]
[笑声]
- This menu has so many choices.
- 这菜单上有这么多选择。
- Ooh, the grass-fed Kobe burger looks good.
- 哦，草饲神户汉堡看起来不错。
- Hey, look!
- 嘿，看！
They have fresh lobster!
他们有新鲜的龙虾！
- Nice!
不错！
I bet the lobster's grass-fed, too.
我打赌那龙虾也是草饲的。
- I'm getting both.
我要两样都点。
I mean, all you have to do is sign for it.
我是说，你只需要签个字就行了。
- Miles, what are you getting?
迈尔斯，你要点什么？
- I'm nauseous,
我有点恶心，
I got seasick in the wave pool.
我在波浪池里晕船了。
FYI: Do not go in the wave pool.
顺便说一句：不要去波浪池。
- Well, let's get to signing.
好吧，我们开始签字吧。
- Do you like clapping at me?
你喜欢对我鼓掌吗？
- It was fun. - Yeah, well,
- 挺好玩的。 - 是啊，
it wouldn't be with broken hands!
- 要是手断了就不好玩了！
So what do you want?
那你想要什么？
Soup of the day is Chunky Clam.
今天的汤是蛤蜊浓汤。
- Oh, please don't say chunky.
- 哦，请别说‘浓’。
- We'll make this easy for you.
- 我们会让你轻松点的。
We'll take one of everything.
我们每样都要一份。
- Fine.
- 好的。
- Oh, just make sure there's plenty of drawn butter
- 哦，确保龙虾有足够的融化的黄油，
for the lobster, and the burger is medium-rare,
汉堡要五分熟，
but leans more rare than medium.
但更偏向于生一点。
[laughter] - And on the onion rings...
[笑声] - 至于洋葱圈...
Hold the onions, just rings.
不要洋葱，只要圈。
- And ranch on the side,
- 旁边要配牧场酱，
but only if it's buttermilk ranch.
但必须是酪乳牧场酱。
If not, blue cheese, but not if it has herbs.
如果不是，那就蓝纹奶酪，但不能有香草。
If it does, I'd rather have non-buttermilk ranch.
如果有香草，我宁愿要非酪乳牧场酱。
- Oh, but if we go that way,
- 哦，但如果那样的话，
I want the onions back in the rings.
我要把洋葱放回圈里。
- Are you guys messing with me?
- 你们是在逗我吗？
- No. This is just how
- 不，这就是
the no-getter / go-getter relationship works.
无为者与有为者关系的运作方式。
- And, uh, my water's not bubbly enough.
- 而且，呃，我的水不够气泡。
- Uh, I'm gonna need a new straw...
- 呃，我需要一根新吸管...
Thanks!
谢谢！
The service here is pretty good.
这里的服务相当不错。
♪ ♪
- Well, boys...
- 好吧，伙计们...
we've eaten every item on the menu.
我们已经吃了菜单上的每一道菜。
- What now?
- 接下来呢？
- Should we hit the wave pool?
我们应该去波浪池吗？
- [groans]
（呻吟声）
- How about we just lie here and get our tan on?
我们躺在这里晒晒太阳怎么样？
- Who wants some sunscreen?
谁想要涂防晒霜？
Whoa!
哇！
- At least the ground won't get burned.
至少地面不会被烧焦。
- I'm really nailing this.
我做得真不错。
Whoa!
哇！
- [gasps]
（吸气声）
It's raining shrimp!
下虾雨了！
- Hallelujah!
哈利路亚！
- It's raining shrimp!
天上下虾雨了！
- Who spilled all the sunscreen?
谁把防晒霜弄洒了？
boys: Uh...
呃...
- Why are you lying in sunscreen?
你为什么躺在防晒霜里？
- Uh...
呃...
- Getting a tan isn't a part of the plan.
晒黑可不是计划的一部分。
Dawn, I'm trying to be nice,
Dawn，我试图友好，
but you're on thin ice.
但你现在处境危险。
I am so in the zone!
我真是进入状态了！
- Please, please, please don't send me
请，请，请不要把我送到洗衣房。
to the laundry room.
托丽！
- Tori!
我的助理刚刚辞职，我快要发飙了！
My assistant just quit, and I'm about to throw a fit!
所以给我找个新人，不然你就完了。
So find me someone new, or you are through.
哦，顺便说一下，
Oh, and FYI,
押韵现在是我的拿手好戏。
rhyming is my thing now.
太好了！
- Yes!
当然，我会给你找个新助理！
Of course, I'll find you a new assistant!
我们有很多优秀的人选。
We've got a lot of great people to choose from.
请，请，请把我送到洗衣房。
- Please, please, please send me to the laundry room.
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
- Look at the go-getter now.
- Huh! Stuck working
for Madison.
- That's not even real pizza.
- Could this summer get any better?
- Could my summer get any worse?
- You know there's a big hole
on this end, right?
在这边，对吧？
- Ugh!
呃！
This is so unfair!
这太不公平了！
I'm stuck here blowing up a pizza raft for Madison
我被困在这里为Madison吹气制作披萨筏
while my brothers get to relax in the sun.
而我的兄弟们却可以在阳光下放松。
- Look at the bright side.
看看光明的一面。
When we get off, we get to play beach volleyball,
当我们下来时，我们可以打沙滩排球，
get mani-pedis--
做美甲和足疗——
- Get in the wave pool?
进入波浪池？
- Uh, maybe not that.
呃，也许不是那个。
Apparently, there was an incident.
显然，发生了一件事。
Just don't let Madison get you down.
只是别让麦迪逊影响了你。
- You know what? You're right.
- 你知道吗？你说得对。
I can do this. Madison is not the boss of me.
我能做到。麦迪逊不是我的上司。
- That's the spirit!
- 这就对了！
Speaking of Madison, she wanted me to tell you
说到麦迪逊，她让我告诉你
she's the boss of you.
她是你的上司。
And you need to take these to Cabana Seven,
而且你需要把这些送到七号小屋，
and tell them the pre-party entertainment starts in 15.
并告诉他们预热派对的娱乐活动15分钟后开始。
- But you just passed Cabana Seven. Why didn't you drop them off?
- 但你刚刚经过了七号小屋。你为什么不放下它们？
- I wanted to...
- 我是想……
b-u-u-u-u-u-t,
但——
Madison said you had to do it.
麦迪逊说你必须做这件事。
Oh, she also made me say it that way.
哦，她还让我这么说。
She also said that if I didn't say it that way, she'd fire me.
她还说了，如果我不这么说，她会解雇我。
She also said that if you screw up, she'd fire me, but she's gonna make you do it,
她还说了，如果你搞砸了，她会解雇我，但她会让你去做，
then she's gonna fire you. - You know what, just give me the bags!
然后她会解雇你。 - 你知道吗，把袋子给我吧！
Hey, at least I don't have to watch my family sleep-gnaw shrimp.
嘿，至少我不需要看着我的家人睡觉时啃虾。
[gnawing]
[啃咬声]
[laughter]
[笑声]
- Knock, knock! Just dropping off a package for-- You!
敲敲门！只是来送个包裹给——你！
[both mumbling] We're the Mermans!
（两人含糊不清地说）我们是梅尔曼斯！
- What the heck are you guys doing here?
你们到底在这里干什么？
- We were leaving, but then there was a mix-up,
我们正要离开，但后来出了点差错，
and then there was sushi, and please don't tell on us!
然后就有了寿司，请不要告发我们！
- But you guys are gonna get me fired!
但你们会害我被炒鱿鱼的！
- No, no, no, relax.
不，不，不，放松点。
No one's gonna find out we're not really the Mermans.
没人会发现我们不是真正的梅尔曼斯。
- Fine. You want to be the Mermans?
好吧。你们想当梅尔曼斯？
Then be the Mermans.
那就当梅尔曼斯吧。
Put these on!
穿上这些！
The show starts in ten minutes!
表演十分钟后开始！
- Ooh, a show.
哦，有表演。
[laughter] - Uh, Tom...
笑声
I think we are the show.
呃，汤姆...
The Mermans are mermaids!
我想我们就是表演。
[laughter]
梅尔曼斯是美人鱼！
- Dawn, you don't really expect us to dress up
笑声
in these ridiculous costumes and put on some dumb show?
唐，你不会真的期望我们穿上这些荒谬的服装，然后表演一个愚蠢的节目吧？
- No...
不...
I expect you to dress up in these ridiculous costumes and put on an amazing show!
我希望你们穿上这些滑稽的服装，然后上演一场精彩的表演！
No sushi for you!
你不配吃寿司！
- Oh!
哦！
- Momma just had to be wild, didn't she?
妈妈总是要这么狂野，不是吗？
♪ ♪
- I like how the lantern looks there...
我喜欢灯笼放在那里的样子...
- Oh, me too!
哦，我也是！
I couldn't think of a better place to put it.
我想不出有比这更好的地方放它了。
- But...
但是...
maybe it'll look better down here on the table.
也许把它放在桌子这里会更好看。
- And you just did!
你刚刚就做到了！
[laughter]
笑声
- Go away.
走开。
- Already gone.
已经走了。
- Hm.
嗯。
What do you think, Dawn?
你觉得呢，Dawn？
- I think it looks better down here.
我觉得放在这里更好看。
- Perfect! Then hang it back up there!
太好了！那就把它挂回那里！
[laughter]
笑声
- Why did you even ask for my opinion?
你干嘛还问我意见？
- So I know what not to do.
所以我知道不该做什么。
I'll go grab the rest of them.
我去拿剩下的那些。
- Oh, no!
哦，不！
- Whoa! - Oh.
哇！哦。
Nice catch.
接得好。
- Thanks. - But I guess
谢谢。不过我想
you're used to things droppin'
你已经习惯了东西掉落，
since you're always droppin' a beat.
因为你总是在打节拍。
- [chuckles] - [nervous laughter]
（轻笑）（紧张的笑声）
I'm gonna pretend I didn't say that.
我还是假装我没说过那句话吧。
- I'm Dylan.
我是Dylan。
- I'm Dawn.
我是Dawn。
So was the song you played earlier for me?
那你之前为我弹的那首歌呢？
- Well...
嗯...
it was for a pretty blonde girl.
那是为了一个非常漂亮的金发女孩。
Here. - Thank you.
这里。
Maybe my summer's starting to look up.
谢谢你。
- Dawn, help us!
也许我的夏天开始有点起色了。
- What happened to you guys?
Dawn，帮帮我们！
- We fell asleep in the sun.
你们怎么了？
- You know, maybe you should just go home.
- 你知道，也许你应该直接回家。
- And say good-bye to our best summer ever?
- 然后告别我们最棒的夏天？
No way!
绝不！
[boys groaning]
[男孩们呻吟]
- Roasted fools.
- 烤焦的傻瓜们。
- Ah. - Boys!
- 啊。 - 男孩们！
- [shrieks] - Wah!
- [尖叫] - 哇！
- It's time to close out your bill.
- 是时候结账了。
- [whimpers]
- [呜咽]
- I got this.
- 我来处理。
Where do we sign?
- Signing time is over.
Now, it's paying time.
- Well, how much do we owe?
- Let's see...
Miles had nothing.
I had an iced tea, that's a buck fifty.
And you guys had one of everything, so that's $320.
- We don't have any money! - We're children!
- Trey, you never said, "Pay later."
- You guys never said you didn't have any money.
- 你们从来没说过你们没钱。
- Who doesn't have any money?
- 谁会没钱？
- Them.
- 他们。
- You know what?
- 你知道吗？
We'll call our parents, and I'm sure they'll be happy
我们会打电话给我们的父母，我相信他们会很乐意
to pay for this bill.
支付这笔账单。
[groans]
[呻吟]
- Are you sure you're not wearing my wig, Tom?
- 汤姆，你确定你没戴我的假发吗？
- Nope.
- 没有。
This one feels right.
这个感觉对了。
[phone ringing]
[电话铃响]
Uh-oh! [phone rings]
哎呀！[电话铃响]
Where's my phone?
我的手机在哪儿？
[phone rings] - [gasps]
[电话铃响] - [吸气声]
Oh! It's in your tail!
哦！在你的尾巴里！
[phone rings] - What? Where?
[电话铃响] - 什么？哪儿？
Oh! [groans]
哦！[呻吟声]
[phone rings] I can't get it.
[电话铃响] 我拿不到。
My mer-skin is too tight. [phone rings]
我的鱼皮太紧了。[电话铃响]
Oh, well.
哦，好吧。
I'm sure it wasn't important.
我相信那不是什么重要的事。
It's show time, Mrs. Merman!
演出时间到了，默尔曼夫人！
- Okay, let's hurry and get our tails out there!
好的，我们快点出去吧！
Go fast!
快跑！
- Something's fishy.
有点不对劲。
They're not answering.
他们没接电话。
- I'm sorry, guys.
对不起，伙计们。
It looks like we're not gonna be able to pay our part of the bill.
看来我们付不起账单了。
- Guys, I think I know how to handle this.
伙计们，我想我知道怎么处理。
Run!
快跑！
- Ow! - Oh, my God!
- 哎哟! - 哦,我的天!
- It hurts! - Ow!
- 好痛! - 哎哟!
- [whimpering]
- [呜咽声]
- Ow! - [shrills]
- 哎哟! - [尖叫声]
- Don't worry...
- 别担心...
I have an idea of how we can work this all out.
我有个主意,我们能解决这一切。
- [exhales]
- [呼气声]
- It's not working!
- 这不管用!
- Just keep your finger on the hole!
- 只要把手指按在洞上!
- You know, this really isn't so bad.
- 你知道,这真的没那么糟糕。
- Madison wants you to scoop out
麦迪逊想让你把冲浪池里漂着的东西都捞出来。
whatever's been floating in the wave pool.
现在，这真的很糟糕。
- Now, it's bad.
最棒的夏天。
- Best summer ever.
没用！
- It's not working!
就用手指按住那个洞！
- Just keep your finger on the hole!
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
欢迎来到麦迪逊最棒夏日启动派对！
- Welcome to Madison's Best Summer Ever Kick-Off Party!
也许如果我们把这些花环都发出去，麦迪逊就会让我们离开这里。
- Maybe if we hand out all these leis,
也许如果我们把这些花环都发出去，
Madison will let us get out of here.
麦迪逊就会让我们离开这里。
- Yeah!
是啊！
- Welcome to Madison's Best Summer Ever Kick-Off Party!
欢迎来到麦迪逊最棒夏日启动派对！
Let's get out of here!
我们离开这里吧！
- Good news!
好消息！
I found more leis.
我找到了更多花环。
- Ahh.
啊。
[laughter]
笑声
- Hey, Dawn!
嘿，Dawn！
- Ooh, can we get some of those?
哦，我们可以拿一些吗？
- Mae, why aren't you in your uniform?
梅，你为什么没穿制服？
- Uh, the snack shack's closed,
呃，小吃摊已经关门了，
and Trey said Miles could bring me to the party.
特雷说迈尔斯可以带我去派对。
But we promise we'll try to act like we're having a bad time
但我们保证会在你看来时尽量装作玩得不开心。
whenever you look over.
哦，我们已经练习过了。
- Oh, we've been practicing.
看。
Watch.
没关系。
- It's okay.
即使这不是我有史以来最好的夏天，
Just because it's not my best summer ever,
也不意味着它不能成为你的。
doesn't mean it can't be yours.
并不意味着它不能是你的。
- So how about those leis?
- 那么那些花环呢？
- Right.
- 对。
- Could you put them on us?
- 你能帮我们戴上吗？
- Okay.
- 好的。
- And could you say the welcome thing again?
- 你能再说一遍欢迎词吗？
- Or we could just come in!
- 或者我们可以直接进来！
- Hey!
- 嘿！
- Oh, hey!
- 哦，嘿！
- So I was wondering if maybe you wanted to hang after the party?
- 所以我在想，聚会后你也许想一起出去玩？
- Yeah! - Sounds good! - I'm down!
- 当然！ - 听起来不错！ - 我赞成！
- Not. You.
- 不。你。
boys: Ah!
男孩们: 啊！
- That'd be great.
- 那太好了。
boys: Ooh!
男孩们: 哦！
boys: Ahh!
男孩们: 啊！
- Sunburn! Sunburn!
- 晒伤！晒伤！
- So, um... can I get your phone number?
- 那么，嗯... 我能要你的电话号码吗？
boys: Ooh!
男孩们: 哦！
Do you mind typing in your number?
你介意输入你的号码吗？
I don't use my D-D-DJ hands.
我不使用我的D-D-DJ手。
- He has a special DJ hand? - That's cool!
- 他有一只特别的DJ手？ - 真酷！
- I wish I had a special hand for something.
- 我真希望我有什么特别的手来做某件事。
[gasps]
[倒抽一口气]
From now on, this is my pudding hand!
从现在起，这是我的布丁手！
Nope. It's my mayonnaise hand.
不，这是我的蛋黄酱手。
- Later when I dedicate a song to a special someone,
- 以后当我为某个特别的人点一首歌时，
you'll know who I'm talking about.
你们就会知道我在说谁了。
boys: Ooh!
男孩们: 哦！
boys: Ow!
男孩们: 哎哟！
- Assistant!
助手！
We have an emergency!
我们有紧急情况！
I need someone to replace the boring rubber bands
我需要有人替换龙虾钳上那些无聊的橡皮筋
on the lobster claws with these official
用这些官方的
Best Summer Ever Kick-Off Party rubber bands.
最佳夏日开幕派对橡皮筋。
- They'll do it! boys: She'll do it!
他们会做的！
- All four of you are gonna do it.
你们四个都要做。
Now, go do it!
现在，去做吧！
Wow, this rhyming thing is fun.
哇，这种押韵的事情真有趣。
- Technically, since you rhymed "do it" with "do it,"
严格来说，既然你用‘做吧’押韵了‘做吧’，
it wasn't actually a--
实际上，那并不算是一个——
never mind, carry on, your rhyme-ness.
没关系，继续吧，你的押韵功夫。
- ♪ To answer the question we get asked most often ♪
- ♪ 回答我们最常被问到的问题 ♪
- ♪ Our top half is human ♪
- ♪ 我们的上半身是人类 ♪
- ♪ Our bottom half is dolphin ♪
- ♪ 我们的下半身是海豚 ♪
both: ♪ Getting fishy with it ♪
两人: ♪ 与鱼共舞 ♪
♪ La, la, la-la ♪
♪ 啦，啦，啦-啦 ♪
♪ Getting fishy with it ♪
♪ 与鱼共舞 ♪
♪ La, la, la-la ♪
♪ 啦，啦，啦-啦 ♪
♪ Getting fishy with it ♪
♪ 与鱼共舞 ♪
♪ La, la, la-la ♪
♪ 啦，啦，啦-啦 ♪
♪ Getting fishy with it ♪
♪ 变得滑稽起来 ♪
- So embarrassing.
- 真尴尬。
- Says the guy who just ate a handful of mayonnaise.
- 说这话的人刚刚吃了一大口蛋黄酱。
- Okay, got all the old rubber bands off.
- 好了，所有的旧橡皮筋都取下来了。
Now we just need to get the new ones on.
现在我们只需要把新的橡皮筋装上。
- Oh, ooh!
- 哦，哦！
Wait, why didn't we think
等等，我们怎么没想到
to put the new rubbers bands on
在取下旧橡皮筋之前
before taking the old rubber bands off?
先把新的橡皮筋装上呢？
- [whispers] Because we're children.
因为我们还是孩子。
- You know what? It seems like
你知道吗？看起来你已经掌控得很好了。
you have this under control.
是啊...
- Yeah...
好吧。
- Fine.
你有兄弟吗？
Do you have brothers?
伙计们，看看这个。
- Guys, check it out.
我们要告诉她吗？
- Do we tell her?
我们必须告诉她。
- We have to.
Dawn！
- Dawn!
你需要看看这个。
You need to see this.
你得看看这个。
- Not now!
- 现在不行！
- No! Now!
- 不！现在！
- [sighs] What?
- [叹气] 怎么了？
Wait, what's going on?
等等，发生什么事了？
- They're holding hands. - Yeah, I can see
- 他们在牵手。 - 是的，我能看出来
what's going on, but I want to know
发生了什么，但我想知道
what's going on.
到底发生了什么。
- So are we still gonna hang after the party?
- 那我们派对后还一起玩吗？
- I don't know if I can.
- 我不知道我能不能。
But...
但是...
when I dedicate a song to a special someone,
当我为某个特别的人点一首歌时，
you'll know who I'm talking about.
你们就会知道我在说谁了。
[both giggle]
[两人轻笑]
- That's what he said to me.
- 他就是这么对我说的。
- We're sorry, Dawn.
- 我们很抱歉，Dawn。
- We've been total jerks to you today.
- 我们今天对你真是太刻薄了。
And now you've gotta go through a horrible heartbreak.
而现在你还要经历这么糟糕的心碎。
- Yeah! That jerk doesn't get to ruin your summer.
- 没错！那个混蛋没资格毁了你的夏天。
We're the jerks who get to ruin your summer.
我们这些混蛋才有资格毁了你的夏天。
- Look, I agree you've been jerks.
- 听着，我承认你们是混蛋。
Big jerks. Huge jerks.
大混蛋。巨大的混蛋。
But don't worry, jerks,
但别担心，混蛋们，
I'm not heartbroken.
我没有心碎。
- What? - You're not?
- 什么？ - 你没有？
- Why not?
- 为什么没有？
- Look, I mean, he's cute and all,
- 听着，我是说，他挺可爱的，
but I just met him today.
但我今天才刚认识他。
And that whole D-D-DJ hand thing is kinda lame.
而且那个D-D-DJ手势有点儿逊。
- But a mayonnaise hand is cool, right?
- 但蛋黄酱手势很酷，对吧？
both: No!
不！
- Anyway, he's not playing me.
反正，他不是在玩弄我。
He's playing her.
他是在玩弄她。
You know what?
你知道吗？
Even though Madison's been nasty to me,
尽管麦迪逊对我很刻薄，
I understand the idea of wanting the best summer ever.
我理解那种想要拥有一个完美夏天的想法。
She shouldn't have her chance of that
她不应该因为一个撒谎的混蛋而失去这个机会。
being ruined by a lying jerk.
听着，麦迪逊，
Look, Madison,
我知道我可能在这里冒着丢掉工作的风险……
I know I may be risking my job here...
但是……
b-u-u-u-u-u-t...
但是...
I need to tell you something.
我有件事要告诉你。
- Okay, buts are my thing. [clears throat] B-u-u-u-u-u-t... go on.
- 好吧，'但是'是我的口头禅。[清嗓子] 但是...继续。
- Okay.
- 好的。
- Hey, Dawn, I got your text.
- 嘿，Dawn，我收到你的短信了。
What'd you wanna talk to me about? - Oh, I just wanted to make sure we're still hanging out later.
你想跟我谈什么？ - 哦，我只是想确认我们稍后还会一起出去。
- You know it.
- 当然。
- So is that why you can't hang out with me later?
- 所以这就是你不能稍后和我一起出去的原因吗？
- Madison?
- Madison？
- You've been playing me.
- 你一直在耍我。
- No, I haven't, I--
- 不，我没有，我--
- Oh, yes, you have, and the player's about to get played.
- 哦，不，你确实有，而且玩家即将被玩弄。
- Not so fast, D-D-DJ!
- 别那么快，D-D-DJ！
- Uh, who-- who are you?
- 呃，你是谁？
- Girlfriend backup.
- 女朋友的支援。
So back up.
所以退后。
- Girls, girls...
- 女孩们，女孩们...
Look, you can't blame me. I'm just trying to have the best summer eve--
听着，你不能怪我。我只是想度过一个最棒的夏日夜晚--
- Oh! - Ooh!
- 哦！ - 哦！
Whaaa! - Didn't expect that!
哇！ - 没想到会这样！
- Ow! Owww!
哎哟！哎哟！
My D-D-DJ hand! [whimpering]
我的DJ手！[呜咽]
- Check it out, everybody.
大家看过来。
The DJ invented a new dance.
DJ发明了一个新舞步。
- Come on! Let's have some fun!
来吧！让我们找点乐子！
- Hey!
嘿！
Thanks for looking out for me.
谢谢你照顾我。
Why'd you do that?
你为什么那么做？
- Oh, well, just seemed like the right thing to do.
哦，嗯，只是觉得那样做是对的。
- Well, thanks.
嗯，谢谢。
But...
但是...
this doesn't make us friends.
这并不意味着我们是朋友。
- Oh, no. Definitely not.
- 哦，不。绝对不是。
- Good. - Good.
- 好。 - 好。
Last words are my thing.
最后的话是我的专长。
- [mockingly] Good. - Heard that.
- [嘲讽地] 好。 - 听到了。
- Oh! - Don't worry, I won't tell anybody.
- 哦！ - 别担心，我不会告诉任何人。
Come on, let's go do the lobster!
来吧，我们去抓龙虾！
[playing The B52's "Rock Lobster" instrumental]
[播放The B52's的《Rock Lobster》器乐]
♪ ♪
[upbeat rock music]
[欢快的摇滚音乐]
♪ ♪